好吧，罗斯
Okay,Ross.
我知道你不想进来看到这个
I realize that you didn't expect to walk in and see that,but..
-可是…听我解释好吗？ -我们什么都没做！
- Let me explain,okay? - We weren't doing anything!
瑞秋，他看到了
Rach,he just saw us.
但你所看到的，就是全部的 知道吗?仅仅一个吻而已
But what you saw,that is the extent of it,okay? One kiss.
-不，天呐，你在说谎。我们在巴贝多就吻过了。 -伙计，冷静点！
- That's a lie! We also kissed in Barbados. - Dude,chill!
好吧，我们在巴贝多也吻过
Okay,we also kissed in Barbados..
可我们没想那样，知道吗？ 发生这件事的唯一原因
but we didn't plan it. The only reason that that happened..
是我看见你吻查莉了。
was because I saw you kiss Charlie.
对，是你开始的！ 我想要冷静的。
Yeah,you started it! I have got to chill.
好吧，我们或许应该在事情 发生之前跟你说
Look,we probably should have talked to you about this before it ever happened.
-可是… -我们对于这感到非常害怕，罗斯
- But.. - Oh,we feel so terrible about this,Ross.
是,对，可它确实发生了
Yeah. But it did happen.
所以…
So..
罗斯？
Ross?
我们可以关上门了么？
Can we just close the door?
罗斯不难过
The.One.Where.Ross.Is.Fine
罗斯,说点什么。
Ross,say something.
什么都行。
Anything.
所以说你们俩…？
So you two are..?
-是。 -是。
- Yeah. - Yeah.
那你们有没有…呃？
And have you had..?
-没，没 -没有。
- No. No,no,no. - No. No.
可如果我没进来的话，你们会不会…？
But if I hadn't walked in here,would you..?
也许。 不,不会!
Probably.. No. No.
罗斯，我们本来没想让你 以这种方式发现。
Ross,this is not how we wanted you to find out about this.
你有权力抓狂。
You have every right to go nuts.
我不会抓狂的。你看我抓狂了?
I'm not going nuts. Do you see me going nuts?
不，可你知道我的意思。
No,but you know what I mean.
如果你们俩开心
If you two are happy..
我也会为你们开心。
then I'm happy for you.
我没事！
I'm fine.
-真的？ -当然。
- Really? - Absolutely.
我没事！
I'm fine.
完全没事！
Totally fine.
我不知道为什么我的声音又大又尖
I don't know why it's coming out all loud and squeaky..
不过说真的。我没事。
because,really,I'm fine.
我不是说我看见你们接吻一点也不吃惊
I'm not saying I wasn't a little surprised to see you guys kissing.
我是说，开始我有点…
I mean,at first I was like:
不过现在我已经开始接受
But now that I've had time to absorb it..
喜欢了。
Loving this.
- 罗斯... -都解决了！
- Ross.. - It's all working out.
我和查莉，还有你们俩。
Me and Charlie. And you two.
-知道我们应该干什么吗？ -冷静下来？
- You know what we should do? - Calm ourselves?
不。
No.
我们应该一起吃顿饭。
We should all have dinner.
对，我们明天晚上就吃。我来做！
Yes,we'll do it tomorrow night. I'll cook!
呃，你不觉得那样太怪了吗？
Look,don't you think that would be a little weird?
怪？为什么?哪儿怪了？
Weird? What? What's weird?
如果有人不喜欢墨西哥菜才是唯一的怪事
The only thing weird would be if someone didn't like Mexican food..
因为我会做“法加它”！！ (一种开胃点心)
because I'm making fajitas!
我非常喜欢法加它。
I do like fajitas.
天呐，领养这件事真让人无法抵抗。
God,this adoption stuff is so overwhelming.
有跨国领养，从属领养…
There's inter-country adoption,dependency adoption.
有这么多方法 这就像我们一生中最大的决定。
There's so many ways to go,and this is,like,the biggest decision of our lives.
我咖啡里有头发。
There's a hair in my coffee.
嗨，伙计们！
Hey,guys.
嗨，你们看见小弗兰克了吗 他要带着他的三胞胎来看我。
Have you seen Frank Jr.? He's meeting me here with the triplets.
知道吗，太有意思了。每次你说“三胞胎”
It's funny,every time you say "triplets"..
我马上就想到三个火辣的19岁金发女郎。
I think of three hot,blond 19-year-olds.
想的美
That's sweet.
喝你的头发吧。
Drink your hair.
嘿，这些是什么？
Hey,what's all this stuff?
哦，这些是我们从不同的 领养中心找来的小册子。
They're brochures from different adoption agencies.
哦，小孩子！ 哦，这个好可爱
Babies! Oh,this one is so cute.
就要这个！
Get this one.
这不是这么用的。
That's not really how it works.
-噢，那怎么用呢？ -我不知道！
- Oh,how does it work? - I don't know!
好吧，如果你们遇到什么困难 可以跟我的朋友们谈谈
If you're having a hard time,you should talk to my friends..
比尔和克琳.  他们领养了个孩子，肯定会帮你们的。
Bill and Colleen. They adopted a kid. I'm sure they'd help you.
谢谢，这太好了。
Thanks,that would be great.
嘿，老公，是不是很棒？
Hey,honey,wouldn't that be great?
好吧，好吧，好吧。 记住我们刚说的。
All right,all right. Remember what we talked about.
在公共场合，要有一定的规矩。
When we're in a public place,there are certain rules.
我们不是这么说的！
That's not what we talked about!
-嗨！弗兰克。 -嗨！
- Hi,Frank. - Hi.
-见到你真好。 -我也一样。
- Good to see you. - Good to see you too.
-嗨，弗兰克. -嗨，过得怎么样？
- Hi,Frank. - Hi. Hey,how you doing?
哦，天呐，他们都这么大了！ 哪个是哪个啊？
Oh,my goodness,they've all gotten so big. Which one is which again?
哦，那个从那个女士包里
Well,that's Frank Jr. Jr..
扯出棉球来的是小小弗兰克。
pulling the tampons out of the lady's purse.
钱德在往钱德身上爬。
And that's Chandler climbing on Chandler.
莱丝莉在往他身上扔百吉饼。
That's Leslie throwing bagels at him.
她扔的真准啊,是不是 不是吗? 是的.
She's got quite an arm there,doesn't she? Yeah.
嗨,伙计们,来给我个拥抱吧.
Hey,guys,come give me a hug.
三胞胎,抱抱你们的姑姑!
Triplets,hug your aunt!
就像抱着刚出炉的饼干.
It's like hugging fresh cookies.
噢,好了.
Oh,okay.
我要吃了你们!
I'm gonna eat you!
你怎么样,弗兰克?
So how you been,Frank?
喔,还好.你知道 生活还不错,一天捱一天
Oh,good,you know. Life is all right. Just taking it day by day.
看起来某个人需要你的某个部件.
Seems like somebody needs something.
噢,不是. 他只是试着 把我的肩膀拽脱臼.
Oh,no. He's just trying to pull my shoulder out of it's socket.
- 噢,我的天. - 没事,我很好.
- Oh,my God. - No,it's fine.
我每次都尝试不让他那么做 但他总能成功,所以..
After I black out,he tries to put it back in,so..
想领养三胞胎吗？ 不！
"Willing to adopt triplets?" No.
呃，我要说我们这么做是为了罗斯 而且这很酷
Can I just say,I know we're doing this for Ross and that's cool.
不过如果让我来定的话 我们第一次约会的时候不会做这个。
But if it was up to me,this is not what we'd be doing on our first date.
那么，我们会做什么？
Well,what would we be doing?
我会带你出去过一个浪漫的夜晚。
I'd take you out for a romantic night.
有香槟，法国大餐 在马车送你回家的路上动手动脚。
Some champagne,fancy dinner,feel you up on the carriage ride home.
动手动脚？
Feel me up?
在马车里面！
In a carriage.
好啦,也许我们应该晚点再约会.
Well,maybe we can have our date later on tonight.
你知道,在这之后,我们会回到我们的房间..
You know,after this,we'll go back to our apartment..
对,对. 是.
Right,right. Yeah.
我们放些音乐,点些蜡烛,然后..
We could put on some music,light some candles,and then..
你想说对我动手动脚,是不是?
You want to say feel me up,don't you?
我只是觉得这是我们应该做的.
I just think it's something we should do.
-嗨，查莉! -嗨
- Hey,Charlie! - Hi.
-嗨 -嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
那么..
So..
- 害怕吗? - 噢,肯定的.
- dreading this? - Oh,you bet.
所以，你给罗斯带来点东西？
So did you bring a little something for Ross?
实际上…这些是你落在我公寓的。
Actually,it's some stuff you left at my apartment.
噢，噢，谢谢。
Well,thanks.
知道吗，你可以随时把我的东西还给我。
And you can just give me my stuff whenever you want.
好，我什么都没丢掉…
Yeah,I didn't throw any of that out.
我说我听到什么声音了！
I thought I heard voices.
嗨，查莉!
Hi,Charlie.
嗨，乔伊
Hey,Joey.
呃…噢！你该向我介绍你的新女朋友。
And,oh,you're gonna have to introduce me to your new girlfriend.
我开玩笑的，我认识瑞秋，我认识。
I'm just kidding. I know Rachel. I know..
进来，请进来。进来。
Come. Please come in. Come in.
好的，呃，我们带来点酒。
Okay. Well,we brought you some wine.
噢！想得真周到。
That is so thoughtful.
她是管家
She's a keeper.
-你又带来了什么？ -呃，实际上，这是…
- And what did you bring me,huh? - Actually,that's..
内裤，牙刷
Underwear,a toothbrush..
还有范海伦的CD。
and a Van Halen CD.
这些我都用得着！！
I can use all these things!
天呐，罗斯，知道吗，你有点…
Gosh,Ross,you know,you seem a little..
什么？心情很好是吗？本来我就是！
What? Fine? Because I am.
你们呢？你们呢？你们呢？ 看到了吗？
Aren't you? Aren't you? Aren't..? You see?
还有谁心情好？
Who else is fine?
好吧
Come on.
听着，嘿，罗斯。放松一点，好吗？ 来喝点什么。
Listen. Why don't you try to relax. Maybe have a drink.
知道吗？这是个好主意。
You know what,that is a very good idea.
我要去弄一大罐马格丽塔酒。
I'm gonna go make a pitcher of margaritas.
噢，我的天。
Oh,God.
真可爱。
So adorable.
看他们睡得就像天使一样。
Look at them,sleeping there like angels.
对，我也很珍惜这段时光
Yeah,I really cherish these moments..
因为你还没意识到它的可贵 他们就会醒过来。
because before you know it,they're gonna be awake again.
嗯，他们可能比较难控制
Well,they may be a handful..
-可他们真得很可爱。 -是啊。
- but they're so cute. - Yeah.
噢，天呐，我最后一次照看他们的时候 他们做了最有意思的事…
Oh,God,last time I babysat them,they did the funniest thing.
我已经4年没睡觉了！
I haven't slept in four years.
这么，这么久了？
That's a long time.
你不知道这有多难，菲比
You just don't know how hard it is,Phoebe.
他们太多了。
There's just so many of them.
知道吗，两个我还能行。
You know,two I could handle.
两个就太好了。你正一手抱着一个
Two's great. You just hold one in each hand.
可第三个带着自行车头盔 朝我跑过来的时候我能怎么办？
What do I do when the third one runs at me with his bike helmet on?
我又没有另一只手来保护我的要害！
I got no more hands to protect my area.
他们是三个，菲比，三个！
There's three of them,Phoebe. Three.
是，我知道，弗兰克。
Yeah,I know,Frank.
我生他们的时候数过了。
I counted them when they were coming out of my area.
有时候我甚至想…
Sometimes,I think that..
哦，不，不，不，我不能说， 太可怕了。不。
Oh,no,no,no,I can't say it. It's too horrible. No.
什么？
What?
不，我不能。
No,no,I can't.
噢，天呐，弗兰克，你想摆脱他们？
Oh,my God,Frank. Are you thinking of leaving?
那三胞胎不算是我的 所以你就想要抛弃他们！
Because I didn't have those triplets so you could run out on them.
噢，不！我永远不会那么做。不。
Oh,no,I would never do that. No. I just..
我只是想，你知道吗 也许你可以带走一个。
was thinking that,you know,maybe you could take one.
什么？！
What?
你不能把他们分开！这太可怕了。 哪一个？
You can't separate them,that's terrible! Which one?
谢谢你能让我们来。
Thank you so much for seeing us.
菲比跟我们说过你们做的好事了。
Phoebe has told us great things about you guys.
噢，请进，我们很愿意帮忙。
Please,we're happy to help.
我们领养的时候也经历过这种事
We went through the same thing when we were adopting.
那么，这间屋子里也充斥着 wee-wee和hoo-hoo的故障声了，呃？
So a lot of malfunctioning wee-wees and hoo-hoos in this room,huh?
我是说，你们的家很温馨。
I mean,you have a lovely home.
好吧，你们说的一切我们都很感激。
We appreciate anything you can tell us.
当然，实际上，我想会有帮助的。
Well,actually,I think this might help.
这些大概就是
It's pretty much..
-你们所需要的所有信息了。 -噢，天呐！
- all the information you need. - Oh,my God.
所有的东西都按类别分开 可以互相引用
Everything is broken into categories,then cross-referenced.
还根据背面的颜色进行了标注。
Then color-coded to correspond with the forms in the back.
太感谢了。
Thank you.
我想我刚经历了一次小高潮。
I think I just had a tiny orgasm.
我知道过程是让人沮丧的 不过是值得的。
I know the process is frustrating,but it's so worth it.
领养欧文是我们经历过的最好的事情。
Adopting Owen was the best thing that ever happened to us.
太棒了。我能看看这本书吗？
That's great. Can I see the book?
你想让我先洗手，是不是？
You want me to wash my hands first,don't you?
这…这个这么漂亮，而且是白的。
Please. It's just so pretty and white.
洗手间在走廊那头，左边。
Bathroom is down the hall to your left.
我也让他这么做过。
I would have told him to do it too.
我能领养你吗?
Can I adopt you?
-嗨，你一定是欧文。 -对。
- Hey,you must be Owen. - Yeah.
我叫钱德。嗨，我也当过童子军。
I'm Chandler. Hey,I was in the Scouts too.
-真的？ -当然，实际上我爸爸是童子军的女训导员。
- You were? - In fact,my father was a den mother.
你知道怎么用指南针吗？
You know how to use a compass?
我得过一枚徽章。
I have a badge in it.
-真的？真是太棒了！ -你想看吗？
- You do? That's fantastic. - You want to see it?
当然想，不过我得先回去跟你的父母聊聊。
I'd love to,but I gotta get back to your parents.
他们在告诉我们怎么领养你的事。
They're telling us about how they adopted you.
什么？！？
What?
怎么了？
我是领养的？
I'm adopted?
我什么都不知道。
I got nothing.
我是领养的？
I'm adopted?
不
No.
我没那么说. 我是说..
I didn't say that. I said..
你是个医生.
you're a doctor.
一个医生.
A doctor.
嗨,大夫，我的胳膊疼. 你能帮我修理一下吗?
Hey,doctor,my arm hurts. Can you fix it for me?
我真不敢相信我是领养的.
I can't believe I'm adopted.
那..你不准备修理我的胳膊了?
So you're not gonna fix my arm?
第一批马格丽塔不是太好
Well,that first batch of margaritas was not so great..
可第二批实在太棒..棒了。
but this second batch is good.
好吧，希望到下一批的时候 我们都能喝一点。
Well,maybe the next batch,we could all get some.
噢，伙计们，这很有趣，是吗？
Oh,God,this is fun,isn't it?
知道吗？就我们四个。
You know,just the four of us.
就这么呆着。
Just hanging.
伙计，你还好吧？
Dude,are you okay?
法加它什么时候才能好？
And when are the fajitas gonna be ready?
我很好！嘿，我很棒！我只是… 我只是为我们而骄傲。
I'm fine,okay? I'm great.I'm just.. I'm just proud of us.
一点都不古怪，一点都不紧张。
You know? There's no weirdness,no tension.
一点都不清醒。
No awareness.
我们组成一个“四人组”。 我们应该一块再做些什么。
We make a great foursome. We should do more stuff together.
哦！ 我们去旅行吧！
Let's take a trip!
我们可以坐你的船去.
We could all go on your boat.
乔伊有一艘很棒的帆船.
Joey has this amazing sailboat.
实际上,罗斯 两年前我已经把船卖掉了.
Actually,Ross,I sold the boat two years ago.
哦,不. 白痴!
Oh,no. Idiot!
呃,是的,不过我可以弄来另外一个.
Well,yeah,but I could get another one.
- 这个旅行听起来棒极了. - 是吗?
- This trip sounds great. - Yeah?
好,你觉得我们能去哪?
Okay,where do you think we can go?
我的法加它!!
My fajitas!
听着，查莉，我只想让你知道。
Look,Charlie,I just want you to know..
罗斯还需要时间习惯我跟乔伊在一起。
Ross is just having a little trouble adjusting to the thought of Joey and me.
知道么，他一般不这么喝酒的。
You know,he normally doesn't drink like this.
噢，你知道吗？这没什么。 我爸爸就是个疯狂的酒鬼。
You know what,this is nothing. My father is a raging alcoholic.
噢，对不起 让你们不舒服了？
I'm sorry,have I made this evening uncomfortable?
法加它!  当心，盘子很烫，盘子很烫！！
Fajitas! Be careful! Very hot plate! Very hot!
罗斯，你怎么没戴手套！
Ross,you don't even have oven mitts on.
明天手要疼了！
That is gonna hurt tomorrow.
好吧，好吧，这太疯狂了。
Okay,well,this is crazy.
我们不可能是在严肃的讨论 我要带走一个孩子，是吗？
We can't seriously be talking about me taking one of your kids,can we?
不，当然不是。
Oh,no,of course we're not.
- 太愚蠢了。 - 我知道。
- That's insane. - I know.
艾丽斯不会支持的，是吗？
Alice would never go for it.
噢，我不知道，她也太累了。 我想她可能会入伙的。
She's pretty tired too. I think we could get her on board.
好吧，知道吗，只是为了争论， 知道吗，是假设的。
Well,just for argument's sake,you know,hypothetically..
你要放弃哪一个？
which one would you be willing to give up?
小小弗兰克?
Frank Jr. Jr.?
对我的胳膊倒是个好事
Well,it'd be great for my shoulder.
噢，你选了这么好的一个。
You'd be getting a really good one.
我是说，知道吗，他真是太有趣了。
He's really funny.
比如，那天他说了个笑话
Like,the other day,he made up this joke:
什么东西是绿的并且说“嗨，我是一只青蛙”？
What's green and says,"Hey,I'm a frog"?
一只会说话的青蛙！
A talking frog.
噢，不，你不能带他走。他太有意思了。
Oh,no,you can't have him,he's too funny.
好吧，好吧，没问题。那莱丝莉呢？
Well,all right,that's fine. What about Leslie?
噢，不，不。不要是莱丝莉。
Oh,no,no,not Leslie. No.
不，她…她是唯一一个会 打着嗝说出字母表来的。
She's the only one that knows how to burp the alphabet.
好吧，那就剩下钱德了。
All right,so that leaves Chandler.
噢，不，不，你不能带走钱德 不。不，不。她是个小天才。
No,no,you can't have Chandler. No,no. She's my little genius.
我对她抱有很大期望。
I got big hopes for her.
她会成为医生或者房地产经纪人…
She's gonna be a doctor or a realtor.
哇，弗兰克。我想我谁都带不走了。
Wow,Frank,I think we just ran out of kids.
噢，我想你是对的。
Oh,I think you're right.
哦，哇，菲比 我不认为我能放弃任何一个。
Oh,wow. Phoebe,I don't think I can give one of them up.
我是说，知道吗 他们让我发疯，可他们是我的孩子。
I mean,you know,they drive me crazy,but they're my babies.
很抱歉，弗兰克。我没想到事情会这样。
I'm sorry,Frank,I didn't realize things were so bad.
知道吗，我会帮你的。
You know,I'll help out more. I can baby-sit anytime you want.
你说一天，我会去的。
You name the day and I'll be there.
-明天怎么样？ -呃，不好。
- How about tomorrow? - Well,that's not good.
不过知道吗，我会推掉其它事 我会到的。
But I can move some stuff around and I'll be there.
你和艾丽斯可以整天呆在一起。
You and Alice just take the whole day together.
你为我们这么做？
You'd do that for us?
你开玩笑吗？你以为姐姐是干什么的？
Are you kidding? That's what sisters are for.
看看他们！
Oh,look at them.
噢，我真爱你们。
I love you so much.
噢，天呐，别醒过来，别醒过来！
Oh,crap,don't wake up! Don't wake up!
-比尔和克琳呢？ -他们在厨房弄点吃的。
- Where are Bill and Colleen? - Kitchen,getting something to eat.
您能想象他们有多好吗？
Can you believe how nice they are?
我们必须走！！
We have to leave.
为什么？你在洗手间做了什么？
Why? What did you do in the bathroom?
我还没去洗手间呢。 我在路上碰到了欧文
I didn't get to the bathroom. I bumped into Owen on the way.
可他还不知道他是被领养的。 有一个小小的机会
He didn't know he was adopted. There's a slight chance..
我告诉了他。
I may have told him.
噢，天呐，我的手袋呢？ 不，我们别管那些了。
Oh,my God,where's my purse? No,I can replace everything in there.
- 拿上活页册，走！ -嗨。
- Get that binder and let's go! - Hi.
给大家的一点小吃。
Some little snacks for everybody.
哦，你们不用吃酸蠕虫， 那是给欧文的。
You don't have to eat the sour worms. Those are for Owen.
我一会儿去叫他。
I'll go get him in a second.
顺便说一句， 你们该知道 我们还没告诉他他是领养的。
By the way,you should know,we haven't told him he's adopted yet.
可孩子们直觉很灵敏。
But kids are so intuitive.
你不认为某种程度上他已经知道了？
Don't you think,on some level,he already knows?
- 我是领养的？！ - 看？直觉！
- I'm adopted? - See? Intuitive.
什么？你从哪儿听来的？
What? Where did you hear that?
他告诉我的！
He told me.
他还给我50块钱让我别说出来。
And he paid me 50 dollars not to tell.
那现在你该把钱还给我了！
Which,technically,now you should give back.
你告诉他他是领养的？
You told him he's adopted?
实在对不起，可你们应该在那儿或者什么地方写明白。
I'm sorry. You should have a sign out there or something.
或者在人们进门的时候悄悄告诉他们：
Or at least whisper it to people when they come in the door.
“欧文不知道他是领养的， 他也认为圣诞老人是真实存在的。”
"Owen doesn't know he's adopted,and he also thinks Santa is real."
他不是吗？！
He isn't?
我们必须走了，亲爱的！
We have to get out of here,baby.
你怎么了？
What is the matter with you?
好了,听着,我知道 钱德做的不是最好的..
All right,look,I know what Chandler did was not the best..
但是任何人都应该想到 一个12岁的孩子会被告知是被领养的
but anyone would assume that a 12-year-old has been told he's adopted.
- 是的,他8岁. - 喔,他长得好高.
- Yeah,he's 8. - Wow,he's tall.
你从哪个国家领到他的?
What country did you get him from?
诸位，我要向
Everyone,I would like to make a toast..
瑞秋和乔伊敬酒。
to Rachel and Joey.
还有爱情。
And to love.
啊，爱情。
Ah,love!
L-O-V-E，爱情。
L-O-V-E. Love.
L是生活。
L is for "life."
没有爱情哪有生活？
And what is life without love?
噢，我的天呐，我们要回答吗？
Oh,my God,are we supposed to answer?
O是
O is for:
“噢，哇！”
"Oh,wow!"
V是
The V is for this..
事情转变的这么快
very surprising turn of events..
而顺便说明，我完全应付得来。
which I am still fine with,by the way.
E是
E..
我发现
is for how..
这是多么的正常。
extremely normal I find it..
你们俩
that you two..
走到了一起。
are together.
有一天你们会结婚
And that one day you might get married..
还会有你们自己的孩子。
and have children of your own.
-伙计，你还好吧？ -完全没问题。
- Dude,are you okay? - Totally.
罗斯，你看起来不太好。
Ross,you don't seem okay.
对不起，一定是快乐的压力太大了。
I'm sorry,it must be the pressure of entertaining.
我想如果我们吃点馅饼会感觉好点。
I think everyone would feel better if we had some flan.
等等，罗斯，我要走了。
Wait,Ross. Ross,I.. I have to take off.
- 不行！ - 对不起
- No! - I'm sorry.
我明天早上还有一节很早的课，
I have an early class in the morning.
不过这已经很好了。
But this has been lovely.
是吗？可你认为跟乔伊一起很不自在
Wasn't it? And you thought it would be awkward with Joey.
而且你从没真正喜欢过瑞秋。
And that you never really liked Rachel.
你过火了！ 我早上给你打电话，好吗？
You are on fire! I'll call you in the morning,okay?
- 好吧。 - 好
- Okay. - All right.
天呐，瑞秋，罗斯刚才说得简直太…
God,Rachel,what Ross just said,that's just..
噢，没事，女孩们从来都不喜欢我。
That's okay. Girls tend not to like me.
再见。
Fine.
好吧，我想只需要给三个人吃馅饼了！
Okay. I guess it's just flan for three.
嘿，嘿，这还挺押韵！
Hey,that rhymes.
知道吗，罗斯？ 我想我们也该走了。
You know what,Ross,I think we're gonna take off too.
噢，噢，当然。天呐，我真蠢。
Of course. God,I'm so stupid.
你们现在是一对了。
You guys are a couple now.
我是说，你们可能想单独待着。
I mean,you probably just want to be alone.
-不，不，我只是说天晚了… -嘿，嘿，没事的。真的没事。
- No,it's just getting late.. - It's fine. It's totally fine.
我已经喝了够多的马格丽塔。真得很好。
I've got plenty of margaritas. It's all good.
我都不知道那是什么。
I don't even know what that's for.
知道吗？
You know what?
我想我应该留下 保证他没事。
I think I'm gonna stay here and make sure he's okay.
-对，这可能是个好主意。 - 对，明天早上见。
- That's probably a good idea. - I'll see you in the morning.
嗯，好吧。
Okay.
知道吗，乔伊
Yeah,you know,Joey,I..
我不认为他会接受我们俩在一起。
I don't think he's ever gonna be okay with this.
看起来不太好，是吗？
It doesn't look good,does it?
我猜我做了土豆泥
I guess I made Tater Tots.
罗斯,手套!
Ross,oven mitts!
早上好。
Morning.
-你醒了。 -谢谢
- Here you go. - Thanks.
-你整个晚上都在这儿? -对。
- Did you stay here all night? - Yeah.
你脱了我的裤子和鞋？
So you took off my pants and shoes?
不，不，不。
No. No,no.
实际上是你跟着《芝加哥》 的原声音乐跳舞时自己脱掉的。
You actually did that when you were dancing to the Chicago soundtrack.
听着，罗斯
Look,Ross..
关于我和瑞秋 听着，你什么都不用担心，知道吗？
about Rachel and I. Listen,you don't have to worry about that..
因为什么都不会发生。
because nothing's gonna happen.
你是什么意思？
What do you mean?
好吧，我们从一开始就说
She and I said from the beginning..
如果你不接受的话我们什么都不会做的。
we weren't gonna do anything unless you were okay with it.
而很明显…
And clearly..
嘿，你在说什么？我很好！
What are you talking about? I'm fine.
- 我们可以继续这样? - 不可以.
- Are we still doing this? - No.
很好，罗斯，好吗？ 我完全明白。
It's okay,Ross. You know,I totally understand.
你当然接受不了。你们是…
Of course you're not fine. You're..
你们是罗斯和瑞秋
You're Ross and Rachel.
除非我们不是。
Yeah,except we're not.
我是说，我们已经有，
I mean,we haven't been a couple in,like..
6年没在一起了。
six years.
噢，天呐，真的吗？
My God,is that right?
有这么久了?
Has it been that long?
我也是这么听说的，是的。
That's what I hear,yeah.
这太疯狂了。我是说，6年？
This is crazy. I mean,six years..
就因为我，你们不能在一起？
and because of me,you guys aren't gonna be together?
我能问你点事吗？
Can I ask you something?
说真的
Really..
你觉得跟瑞秋在一起怎么样？
what is this thing with you and Rachel?
别闹了，我是说，你了解我，你知道…
Come on,you know me. You know..
乔伊
Joey.
我为她感到疯狂。
I'm crazy about her.
她也这么想吗？
And she feels the same way?
我想是的。
I think so.
好吧，那么
Well,then..
可能现在我们都该往前看了。
maybe it's time we all moved on.
对，不过，罗斯 我是说，你并没有完全接受。
Yeah,but,Ross,I mean,you're not okay with it,so..
不，我会的。
No,but I want to be.
嘿，我会的。
I will be.
另外，我还有查莉呢，对吧？
Besides,I'm with Charlie,right?
噢，天呐，我还跟查莉在一起呢,是吗？
Oh,my God,I'm still with Charlie,aren't I?
-我是说，她没看见我跳舞吧？ -不，不，不，不
- She didn't see the dance,did she? - No,no,no.
只有 只有我看见了。
No,that was.. That was just for me.
你……
Hey,you..?
你说真的？
You sure about this?
对，我是说真的。
Yeah,I'm sure.
那...
And..
我们的关系没问题吗？
we're okay?
- 嗨，菲比 - 嗨。
- Hey,Phoebe. - Hey.
呃，我们只是想给你提个醒。
We just want to give you a heads up.
- 比尔和克琳讨厌我们。 - 为什么？
- Bill and Colleen hate us. - Why?
欧文不知道他是领养的， 可莫妮卡告诉了他。
Owen didn't know he's adopted and Monica told him.
什么？
What?
- 他不知道?他12岁了啊. - 不,他才8岁.
- He didn't know? He's 12. - No,he's only 8.
我打赌他是俄罗斯人.
I'll bet he's Russian.
可是，他总有一天会发现的。
Still,he had to find out sometime.
对，可如果有人告诉这三胞胎 是你生的他们 你会高兴吗？
How would you like it if someone told the triplets that you gave birth to them?
我要去告诉艾玛，说她是个事故的结果。
I'm gonna go tell Emma she was an accident.